/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data7_1', {
    title: '7.1 Multiplying Fractions',
    path: '7.1-multiplying-fractions',
    children: [{
        title: 'Multiplying Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{2}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{3}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{3}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{2}}}{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{3}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{6}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiplying Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{6}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{12}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{4}}}{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{6}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{24}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiplying Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\frac{\\str{6}}{\\str{8}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\str{10}}{\\str{9}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\input{6}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{6}}{\\str{8}}}{\\frac{\\str{10}}{\\str{9}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{60}}{\\str{72}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiplying Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\str{6}}{\\str{2}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{3}}{\\input{2}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{6}}}{\\frac{\\str{6}}{\\str{2}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{18}}{\\str{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiplying Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\frac{\\str{42}}{\\str{8}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\str{12}}{\\str{14}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{9}}{\\input{2}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{42}}{\\str{8}}}{\\frac{\\str{12}}{\\str{14}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{504}}{\\str{112}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiplying Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\str{20}}{\\str{35}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{10}}{\\input{7}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{6}}}{\\frac{\\str{20}}{\\str{35}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{300}}{\\str{210}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiplying Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\frac{\\str{63}}{\\str{72}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\str{64}}{\\str{99}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{56}}{\\input{99}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{63}}{\\str{72}}}{\\frac{\\str{64}}{\\str{99}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{4096}}{\\str{7128}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiplying Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\str{10}}{\\str{18}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{20}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{4}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{5}}}{\\frac{\\str{10}}{\\str{18}}}{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{20}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{450}}{\\str{1800}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiplying Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\frac{\\str{12}}{\\str{24}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\str{36}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\str{18}}{\\str{32}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{27}}{\\input{16}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{12}}{\\str{24}}}{\\frac{\\str{36}}{\\str{6}}}{\\frac{\\str{18}}{\\str{32}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{7776}}{\\str{4608}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiplying Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\html{Solve &nbsp;}}{\\frac{\\str{65}}{\\str{77}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\str{55}}{\\str{104}}}{\\sign{&times;}}{\\frac{\\str{84}}{\\str{132}}}',
                answer: '\\frac{\\input{25}}{\\input{88}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Multiply the fractions together.}',
                answer: '\\multiplyfracs{\\frac{\\str{65}}{\\str{77}}}{\\frac{\\str{55}}{\\str{104}}}{\\frac{\\str{84}}{\\str{132}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Reduce the fraction to its lowest terms.}',
                answer: '\\prev{feedbackData.getPrevious()}{\\reducefrac{\\frac{\\str{300300}}{\\str{1057056}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }]
});
